

# **BABAR ALI**

Full Stack Web Developer

## **My Contact**

ba2497195@gmail.com

**(** +923012423111

Village Sarhal, District Sialkot

#### Skill

- HTML
- css
- Javascript
- React.Js
- Node.JsWordpress

#### **Soft Skill**

- Great communication skills with client.
- Ability of mentorship for newer developers
- Problem solving skills.
- Multi-tasking

## **Education Background**

- BS (Hons.) Information Technology University of gujrat
   2015-2019
- ICS
   Govt.Allama Iqbal Post Graduate
   College,Sialkot
   2013 2015
- MatriculationGovt.High Secondary School Merajky

2011 - 2013

#### **About Me**

I am Full Stack Developer with 3+ Years' experience in web development seeks a position in your firm with aim to contribute to its organization and client development by effective web application creation and ensuring innovative self maintenance done by the program itself.

## **Professional Experience**

Senior Web Developer | SHARA Web Solution 2021 - 2023

Key responsibilities:

- As Developer, I worked on advance and multiplatforms alongoids
- platforms alongside
  - team of IT professionals in developing different
    website a aplications using latest technologies as
    Frontend development with Html ,CSS JavaScript
    and wordpress. I also worked in React.JS, Backend
    Development with Node.js and MongoDB and
    MySQL. I am responsible of
    developing,integrating,testing and maintaining web
    applications.
  - I worked as project manager in company
  - I also worked as Sales executive

## **Volunteer work**

Freelauncer web developer 2019-2021

Key responsibilities:

- HTML 5 Banner adds animated
- Front end web application development
- programing in c++
- Digital Marketing

#### **Tools & Framework& Libraries**

- Github
- Vercel
- VS Code
- Firebase
- Figma

- React Router
- Redux
- Mongoose
- Express JS
- React Bootstrap